I wonder if that man, Hiraku Machio,
has been doing well.
Having wondered how he was faring,
I decided to observe him.
I am God.
The salvation of souls is part of my job.
However, even God makes mistakes.
I mistakenly bestowed a life of suffering
fit for a sinner upon an innocent man.
Interfering after someone has
started their life is against the rules.
In an attempt to make up for what I'd done,
I gave him a chance at a second life
per his wishes, however...
Isn't this forest in a dangerous area
filled with wicked nasty monsters?
I'm pretty sure it's called The Forest of Death...
The Forest of Death
He was thrown in there all alone
and told to sustain himself by farming.
What kind of twisted game is this?!
I need to call him back right away... but no!
I just said that would be
an infraction of the rules!
There's a chance he'll find his way
back here again as a soul.
If that happens, I hope he accepts my apology.
Even God... makes mistakes.
Farming Life in Another World
Here are the results from me having used
the almighty farming tool for a while.
I've been able to learn several things.
First, there are the crops that I was able
to grow without planting any seeds.
There are potatoes,
onions,
tomatoes, and...
cabbage as well as others.
These are the exact plants I was thinking about
while I was tilling the land earlier.
If I imagine the plants I want to grow
while I'm using the almighty farming tool,
Eggplant! Eggplant! Eggplant! Eggplant!
If I imagine the plants I want to grow
while I'm using the almighty farming tool,
those seeds become sowed in the ground.
I... want... spinach!
When I looked for proof so that
I could put this theory to the test...
here's what happened.
I wanted something that I'd be able to identify
as soon as it sprouted,
Bean sprouts! Bean sprouts! Bean sprouts!
so I thought about how much
I wanted soybeans while I was tilling.
Bean sprouts!
And that's exactly what I got.
I'm sure these will continue
growing into soybeans.
For now, I'll just sit back and watch.
Crops I planted with the almighty
farming tool grow very quickly.
Actually, sometimes they grow so fast I find
myself thinking "Oh crap!" after they pop up.
These potatoes, for example, turned green
where the sun was hitting them.
If my memory serves correctly,
potato sprouts are poisonous.
I'm too afraid to try eating these.
To prevent this from happening again,
I think it's best to put a little mound of soil
near the plant's base.
I didn't have any idea what I was going on
when I looked at crops in my previous life,
but I'm sure the farmers had all kinds of
knowledge they learned from their experiences.
My only option now is to press on
and learn from my mistakes.
Anyways, the only reason I'm able to
live a life of farming here
is by the grace of the Gods.
That's why I decided to make
some statues of them.
Just so you know,
the one on the left is supposed to be
the God with jurisdiction over agriculture.
It feels like things are getting
more civilized around here.
Thank you, Gods.
I'm living a very primitive lifestyle here.
Today's lunch is a stew
made from rabbit meat
and super fresh farm-to-table vegetables
grown without any pesticides!
In other words, I just boiled stuff.
I don't have anything to season it with.
Mmmm, organic.
Plus the meat from the animals
is a lot easier to eat
if I drain the blood as soon as I kill them.
The dogs like eating the meat from the animals
I drained the blood from properly, too.
Sometimes I worry that
I've spoiled them with this food.
Oh well. As long as they're enjoying it,
then it's fine.
I wish I had some salt, though.
I decided to try my hand at something new.
I know it's hard to tell now,
but I planted some fruit bearing trees here.
If this goes well,
my diet will instantly improve, but...
Apples!
If this goes well,
my diet will instantly improve, but...
Pears! Pears!
they say that fruit trees take years
to bear fruit, so I'll need patience.
Persimmons! Persimmons!
they say that fruit trees take years
to bear fruit, so I'll need patience.
Persimmons!
I'm prepared to wait as long as I need to.
Go!
Good boy! Good boy!
Life with the dogs is really fun.
The loneliness might have been unbearable
if I didn't have them here.
A horn?
Well, I am in a different world.
I guess dogs have horns here.
They're all waiting their turn.
There's another thing that having the dogs
here really helps out with.
They can travel through the forest
without getting lost.
Thanks to that, I can explore
even further into the forest.
And eventually...
I found a river that could
act as a source of water.
There's a little waterfall upstream
that raises the river up a level.
I think I might be able to dig out a path
for that water to run to my home.
It's a 30-minute walk, so I'd have to do a lot of digging...
but it'll be fine if I work at it little by little.
I figured I'd be working away
from home for a while,
so I built myself a toilet
at the construction site.
Yup. Nice and civilized.
I turned the almighty farming tool
into a wheelbarrow.
I don't tire out at all while using
the almighty farming tool,
so now I can travel around without
getting tired and speed up construction.
I think I need to fix the roads first.
Back at the home base,
I've cleared out more of the forest
and continued expanding my crop fields.
I'm growing oilseed rape crops
to harvest their oil.
Oilseed Rape
You can get oil
from their seeds
It's the plant rapeseed oil comes from.
Wheat.
Wheat
Pretty easy
to preserve
It's easy to preserve, and I can use it for
all kinds of different stuff if I turn it into flour.
Sugarcane, because I want something sweet...
Sugarcane
Sweet
By the way, those bean sprouts
grew into soybeans before I knew it.
I wanted to eat some edamame, but...
I need salt to make it,
and I don't have any.
I wonder if there's any rock salt around here.
Farming Life in Another World.
Fruit trees
River and waterfall
New crop fields
How long has it been
since I started living here?
One day, it started to get cold.
Honestly, it's too cold
to be in these clothes now.
I can see snow on the mountains
in the distance.
I wonder how cold the winters here get.
I need to do something
to prepare for the cold.
I tried to use the pelt from the giant rabbits,
but they smelled awful
and I was worried that they would
start rotting, so I gave up on them.
I guess my only option is to
light a fire a stay inside my hut.
I'll need to gather firewood
and food for the winter.
A giant black seat cushion?
Wait, is that a spider?
This looks like some really nice cloth.
Is it a handkerchief?
They even embroidered it!
That's amazing. Thank you.
The spider started living up in the giant tree.
And their favorite food is potatoes.
It's not just cloth,
they can even make clothes really well.
They actually managed to turn the animal pelts
I'd given up on into some nice stuff.
I can handle the cold with this!
Bedding stuffed with leaves!
Civilization
Curtains that block the wind!
Just having stuff made from cloth now
has made this place much more civilized.
By the way, I gave the spider a name.
Zabuton
Based on my first impression,
I called them Zabuton.
Now I have someone else
I can count on living here.
Winter finally arrived.
It's gotten pretty cold outside,
but thanks to the preparations I made,
I'll make it through fine.
The dogs are all cozy inside.
Zabuton might be hibernating or something,
because they haven't come down
from the tree lately.
It snows here, but thankfully
it doesn't pile up too much.
If this region got heavy snow fall,
it would have already flattened my hut.
I am still a little worried.
The food stored ahead of time
should be enough to last.
I don't have any real problems living here now,
but I do wish I had some salt.
For some reason I've been feeling
really lonely lately.
It's cold...
How long has it been
since I've talked to someone?
At this rate, I might forget how to talk.
Eventually, the cold started to ease up.
The snow began to melt.
And before long, it felt like spring.
Around that time, something was
happening with the puppies.
They all entered the forest.
It was time for them to leave the nest.
Seeing them grow up so well
brought me some joy, and some sadness.
As I found myself starting to get lost
in those kinds of thoughts...
This is nature...
They came back a few days later.
Apparently, they had all gone
looking for partners.
I wonder if he got into a fight with a rival.
It's not easy being a dog.
And there was one more surprise.
After not having seen them for a while,
Zabuton showed up with a bunch of kids.
I guess she was a female...
Well, this is all good news.
Everyone has a bigger family now.
To be honest, I'm jealous.
And so, there were more mouths to feed.
That meant it was time to work even harder
at expanding my crop fields.
That's...
Zabuton's ringing the alarm?
Is something nasty heading this way?
Kuro led me into the middle of the forest.
Meeting someone new
always happens as a surprise.
That's definitely...
a little girl.
Why is she in the middle of the forest here?
Why is she in this condition?
Hey, wait!
Help me! Please!
We can understand each other...
Okay.
I'm not sure what's going on here,
but it's been a long time since I've heard
someone else's voice.
She grew?
Thank you for saving me.
Who the heck is she?
Is she a monster or
something dangerous like that?
Wait! No! Stop!
Stop it! Paw! Wait, I mean sit!
She got small again.
So... like, are you... my enemy?
Are you here to hurt us?
No! Stop siccing your dogs on me!
But you sucked my blood just now.
I'm sorry, but I couldn't help it!
It's because of them!
Come on, stop it!
Well, she seems harmless enough.
According to her, us meeting
was a complete coincidence.
And the reason she sucked my blood
was to recover her strength.
She said that she used too much energy
and couldn't maintain her body form
or her clothes anymore.
Why did they all even attack her
in the first place?
I thought I could take on one of them...
Okay then. So she was the one
who attacked first.
That said, I felt bad at how hard
they'd beaten her up,
so I offered to let her suck some more
of my blood so that she could recover.
It feels like she's sucking a lot of my blood...
but I don't feel any effects from it at all.
Is this another one of the perks
of a healthy body?
I've never tasted blood so full of vitality!
You must be living a healthy life.
What?
Aren't you smaller than last time?
Huh? But if I suck any more of your blood,
your life will be in danger.
Don't worry about it.
Take as much as you want.
O-okay...
I can't believe there's a place like this
in the middle of this forest!
Are all of these crops yours?
I've never seen this plant before.
What's this?
The one here with the red fruit.
They're very pretty.
Are they decorative plants?
They're tomatoes.
Have you never seen them?
No, this is the first time.
I see. I guess they aren't normal here.
Let's see. Which one looks good?
Here. Want to try one?
You can eat them just like that?
The texture is strange, but...
it tastes wonderful!
It's so juicy!
It really is nice to hear
someone praise your work.
Hey, I want to see your other crops.
Sure.
I never imagined that I'd ever
be able to learn about
so many new species in a single day!
I guess that thing is magic.
Makes sense. I'm in a different world.
Her name is Lu Lulucy.
She's a vampire.
Well, she already sucked a lot of my blood
so I shouldn't really be surprised now.
She said that she's doing
research on medicinal plants.
And the reason she came to this forest was...
I got into a little fight with some nobles.
They were trying to steal
my research away from me.
After I ran away, they sent a real
pain in the ass to chase me down.
I decided it would be best for me to
lay low somewhere until things cooled off.
That's when I heard about this forest.
I thought coming here might
help along my research as well,
but this is more than I imagined.
I wonder how many days it'll take me
to inspect everything here.
It's all very intriguing.
Well, I did almost get wiped out earlier.
This place really does live up to
its savage reputation.
Hm? Its reputation?
You don't know? But you live here.
Yeah...
And you tamed all those beasts...
I'm not really sure
what you're talking about.
Anyways, about that magic you're using...
I've never seen any techniques
used to create stuff like that.
Is that some kind of magic tool?
A magic tool? Maybe.
Oh my, what a day it's been!
I've lived a long life, but I guess there are
still a lot of things left for me to learn.
She's right.
It's been a day of surprises.
I can't believe I met her.
That's right.
I don't know if something like this
will ever happen again.
Hey, are you planning on
continuing to live here?
If you are, would it be alright if
I came to visit again some time?
I have a request!
If...
If it's alright with you,
would you stay here with me?
Huh?
Well it'd be grateful if I could stay here
to work on my research a little longer...
I want you to live here with me!
I want you here forever!
Huh? D-do you mean...
Exactly!
W-wait. Hold on!
This is all so sudden!
I don't want to let this chance get away!
But, I told you before...
there are people who are after me.
I don't care.
I'm a vampire!
Not a problem!
I'm surprised myself.
I've never been good at
dealing with other people.
The reason I came here was so that I could
live on my own, away from people.
But living here alone...
I don't know how many more years
I can handle that.
Okay, fine.
I'm okay with it, but...
it's just all so sudden.
So then...
Then what?
Um, I'm okay with staying to live here.
It's not like I have anywhere else to go.
Really?
But we really have only just met each other.
We can get to know each other
while we're living together.
It's just... so sudden.
It was such a sudden proposal...
Proposal?
You told me to stay and
live here with you, right?
Oh yeah.
It's pretty lonely here, so I thought it
would be nice if you were here with me.
When you asked me to be with you forever,
that's what you meant, isn't it?!
You're getting embarrassed now?!
No, it's just...
Okay. So I proposed to you.
Is that not what you meant?
It is what I meant!
In fact, it's exactly what I want!
I implore you!
Stop! Alright already.
Jeez... I told you okay, didn't I?
Yay!
Thank you!
I told you, you're moving too fast!
Good morning.
I never thought a simple greeting
could make me so happy.
Why did you get small again?
It's for my own protection.
You won't think about touching me
as long as I look like this, right?
Y-yeah... I'll restrain myself.
So what are you working on now?
Well, I was thinking of trying to grow
sweet potatoes next.
Oh?
They're easy to prepare and eat,
and they preserve well.
And now we have more people living here.
That's right, you're the first person
to move in here.
That makes you the first villager here.
What do you mean?
This is a village?
Well, not yet. It's still not at that level.
You guys were living here first, weren't you?
Then there's Zabuton and her family.
And she's got a bunch of kids.
So Lu, that makes you...
about the 30th villager, I think.
What kind of title is that?
Does it even matter at that point?
I wanted to ask, do you think we can
grow medicinal herbs in this field?
I think we might be able to.
Let's try it and find out.
Yeah!
We'll have to find some way
to get our hands on the right seeds.
Nope. We don't actually need any seeds.
Huh? Why not?
Yeah... I remember we talked about
The Forest of Death on
the other side of the mountain.
I see.
Man, I've been seeing a lot of
strange customers in here lately.
I don't know if you're searching for someone
or what, but you should give up.
Unless you can sprout wings and fly, that is.
Very well. I understand.
Thank you for your kindness.
Next time
Episode 3
More and More New Roommates
Next time